Guide to the Ron Howard papers, 1958-1999 MS0766.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Slides, 1958-1983; MS0766 Series 2; 1 Linear foot (Box SHARED Box 11)
  This series compliment the photos and are contained in 6 trays (1.0 linear foot), or approximately 3,000 images. They range in date from 1958-83, with the bulk from 1970-80. The series is arranged alphabetically by subject and vary somewhat from the photo series. Major subjects include Basketball (from 1968-1983), Buildings (including Bacon Hall, Gelman Library, Marvin Center, Rice Hall), Commencements, Distinguished Alumni Award Winners, Drama at the Marvin Theater, GW's 150th Anniversary, Individuals (including GW faculty Marcus Cunliffe, John Latimer, Elmer Kayser, John Boswell) Student/Campus Scenes, Personalities (including Muhammad Ali, Pearl Bailey, Neil Armstrong, Everett Dirksen, Gerald Ford, Herbert Hoover, Harry Truman, Robert and Ted Kennedy, Queen Elizabeth, Ronald Reagan, Elizabeth Taylor, Earl Warren).
  The Washington Scenes sub-series contains subjects including Arlington Cemetery and John F. Kennedy's gravesite, the Capitol, 4th of July fireworks on the Mall, the Jefferson and Lincoln Memorials, and the White House. It also contains scenes from the NBC news program "Meet the Press," with guests dating from 1965-1975.
  The final sub-series contains Mr. Howard's personal slides (as with the photo series), and features approximately 100 images from a trip he took to the former U.S.S.R. in 1983.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Alumni Association, Basketball, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1971-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 2)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 3)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 4)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 7)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 8)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 9)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 10)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1979-1980 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 11)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1981-1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 12)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1981-1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 13)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 14)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 15)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 16)
    Buildings photographed include: Bacon Hall,1980; Burns Library; Funger Hall,1970-1971; Gelman Library,1973-1974; Hall of Government,1966; Hospital,1975; Lisner Auditorium,1972; Lisner/Marvin Center,1971; Lisner Library,1965; Lisner Hall,1965; Marvin Center,1970-1972; Maury Hall,1970; Monroe Hall,1971; Old President's Office,1965; Rice Hall,1967-1970; Rice Hall,1967; Stockton Hall,1971; Woodhull House (left).
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 17)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 18)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Campus Construction, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 19)
    Campus Construction photographs include: Rice Hall,1972; Parking Garage (22nd and I),1972; Marvin Center,1972; Campus,1972.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Campus Construction, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 20)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Campus Scenes-Alumni House, 1980 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 21)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Campus Scenes-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 213, Folder 22)
    Includes the following images: 21st & I looking south,1971; Washington Circle,1969; 21st & H street, vista north,1971; 21st & G (Quigley's on right),1971; Penn Ave. at 22nd street,1972; View from Rice Hall looking west,1971; Fraternity House,1975.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Classroom Scenes, Commencement, 1965 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 23)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Buildings- Maury Hall, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 24)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 25)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 26)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 27)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 28)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 29)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1972-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11)
    General
    Located in Box 17 of shared box.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, Gene Fodo, Arch Bonny, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Distinguished Alumni Awards, 1983, Drama-Plays in Marvin Center, 1971-1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 10)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Plays in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 11)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Plays in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 12)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Plays in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 13)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Plays in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 14)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Marvin Center backstage scenes, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 15)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-James Whitmore performs at Marvin Center, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 16)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Drama-Play at Rathskeller in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 17)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Exhibit in Gelman Library, Special Collections, 1975, Farewell for Ginny Barncastle, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 18)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Fraternities, 1966-1967 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 19)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, w/Mark Hatfield, Lloyd Elliott, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 2)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Functions, 1966-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 20)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Functions, 1966-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 21)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Functions, 1966-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 22)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: GWU's 150th Anniversary, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 23)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: George Washington Awards, GW Bust Ceremony (Eye street Mall), 1980 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 24)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: George Washington, Houdon Statue, GWU Seal, GWU Welcomes Metro Glee Club/Troubadors, 1974, 1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 25)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Individuals, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 26)
    Individuals photographed include: Skip Gnehm, 1966,1980; Skip Gnehm, Bob Ferris,1980; Skip Gnehm, Lloyd Elliott,1980; Marcus Cunliffe,1982; Marcus Cunliffe, E.K. Morris,1980; Averall Harriman; Flip Wilson,1968; Gerald Ford; Senator Henry Jackson; John Latimer; Seymour Alpert,1973; E.K. Morris (Chairman, Board of Trustees),1971; Elmer Kayser; Lloyd Elliott,1974; Elmer Kayser,1966; Dennis O'Leary (Alumni Association);Judge Sarah Hughes,1982; J. William Fulbright; John Boswell.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Individuals, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 27)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Lloyd Elliott, GW President, Martha's Marathon, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 28)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Musical Performance in Marvin Center, 1975 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 29)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1980 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 3)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Office Scenes, 1966-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 30)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1981 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 4)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement-Winter Commencement with Marcus Cunliffe, 1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, spring semester, 1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Commencement, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 7)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Development Office, 1973-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 8)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Distinguished Alumni Awards, 02/1981 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11)
    Located in Box 18 of shared box.
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Snowfall GWU Campus, 1979 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Staff, 1970-1995 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 2)
    Includes: Plaque for Melville Grovsenor (trustee),1974; Bob Ferris, Joann Warner,1980; Cathy Picar (Choral Director), 1982
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Student protests, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 3)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Students/Campus, 1966-1980 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 4)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Telethon in Lisner Auditorium with Andy Williams, Perry Como, Eddie Fisher, Robert Kennedy, 02/1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Telethon in Lisner Auditorium with Andy Williams, Perry Como, Eddie Fisher, Robert Kennedy, 02/1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Telethon in Lisner Auditorium with Andy Williams, Perry Como, Eddie Fisher, Robert Kennedy, 02/1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 7)
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: University Yard, 1961-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 8)
    Tray also contains personalities: Agnew, Spiro,1968; Ali, Muhammad,1969; Armstrong, Louis,1961; Astronauts (Aldrin, Collins, Armstrong),1969; Astronauts Apollo 11,1969; Bailey, Pearl,1975; Borman, Frank,1967; Buchwald, Art,1972
  - George Washington University, Events, and Campus: Personalities, 1967-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 9)
    Tray contains: Buckley, William F.,1967; Child, Julia; Clifford, Clark and Ted Kennedy,1970; Collins, Michael,1969; Cox, Archibald,1973; Denver, John,1967; Devane, William,1975; Dirksen, Everett,1969
  - Personalities, 1964-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 10)
    Tray contains: Chisolm, Shirley; Eisenhower, David;Erlichman, John,1972; Ford, Betty,1974; Ford, Gerald, 1972, 1974,1975; Ford, Gerald and Bowie Kuhn,1975; Ford, Gerald and Bill Buckley,1975; Ford, Tennesee Ernie,1970; Fulbright, J. William,1974; Galway, James,1980; Godfrey, Arthur,1972; Goldwater, Barry, 1964,1975
  - Personalities, 1962-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 11)
    Tray contains: Goldwater, Barry, 1964,1975; Hartman, David; Hatfield, Senator Mark,1971; Heston, Charleton; Hirt, Al,1970; Hoover, Herbert,1962; Hoover, Herbert and Harry Truman,1962; Humphrey, Hubert,1967-1968
  - Personalities, 1967-1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 12)
    Tray contains: Humphrey, Hubert,1967-1968; Inoyue, Senator Daniel,1973; Jackson, Senator Henry,1967; Kennedy, Ethel,1970; Kennedy, Jackie,1972
  - Personalities, 1970-1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 13)
    Tray contains: Kennedy, Jackie,1972; Kennedy Center,1972; Kennedy, John F.,1963; Kennedy, Joan and Alan King,1970; Kennedy, Robert F. house,1970; Kennedy, Robert F. estate,1970; Kennedy, Rose,1970
  - Personalities, 1969-1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 14)
    Tray contains:Kennedy, Ted,1970; King, Alan,1970; King, Alan and Ted Kennedy,1970; Kissinger, Henry,1972-1973; Kissinger, Henry and Mrs. Lace,1973; Lovell, Jim,1969
  - Personalities, 1968-1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 15)
    Tray contains: Lovell, Jim,1969; Mansfield, Mike,1971; McCarthy, Eugene,1968; McGovern, George,1971; McNamara, Robert,1968; Mitchell, John,1972; Muskie, Edmund,1969-1970; Newman, Edwin,1968; Nixon, Pat,1968; Nixon, Richard,1968
  - Personalities, 1968-1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 16)
    Tray contains: Nixon, Richard,1968-1970; Nixon, Richard with Shah of Iran,1973; Prince Phillip,1969; Queen Elizabeth
  - Personalities, 1966-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 17)
    Tray contains:Queen Elizabeth with Gerald Ford,1975; Reagan, Ronald, 1966,1974; Rockefeller, Nelson, 1965,1971; Rogers, Roy,1974; Rumsfeld, Donald with Ron Howard,1971; Rusk, Dean,1968; Sanders, Harlan,1971
  - Personalities, 1970-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 18)
    Tray contains: Schuler, Robert,1975; Scott, Willard,1970; Steinbrenner, George,1982; Swanson, Gloria,1971; Taylor, Elizabeth,1980; Tower, John,1969; Truman, Harry S.,1962; Vanocur, Sander,1968; Wallace, George,1971; Washington, Walter,1970; Walters, Barbara,1972
  - Washington Scenes-Aerial images of DC, 1962-1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 19)
    Tray also concludes Personalities slides: Warren, Earl,1962; Weinberger, Caspar,1974; Westmoreland, William,1967; Wilson, Flip,1968; Woodward, Bob and Carl Bernstein
  - Washington Scenes-Arlington Cemetery, 1964-1965 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Washington Scenes-Arlington Cemetery, 1967-1969 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Washington Scenes-Arlington Cemetery, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Washington Scenes-Capitol, 1965-1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Washington Scenes-Carter, Jimmy Inaugural, 1977, Dwight Eisenhower funeral, 1969 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Washington Scenes-Fireworks, 1964-1969 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Washington Scenes-Fireworks, 1972-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Washington Scenes-Fireworks, 1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Washington Scenes-Fireworks, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Washington Scenes-Ford's Theatre with Ted Kennedy et al, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Washington Scenes-Fourth of July Parade DC, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11)
    Located in Box 19 of shared box.
  - Washington Scenes-Fourth of July Parade DC, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Washington Scenes-Fourth of July Parade DC, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Folder 19, Folder 2)
  - Washington Scenes-Fourth of July Parade DC, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Washington Scenes-Hirshorn Gallery, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Washington Scenes-Honor America Day, 07/1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Washington Scenes-Honor America Day, 07/1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Washington Scenes-Honor America Day, 07/1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Washington Scenes-Honor America Day, 07/1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Washington Scenes-Honor America Day, 07/1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Washington Scenes-Jefferson Memorial, 1966-1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Washington Scenes-Johnson Inaugural, 1965 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Washington Scenes-Kennedy Center, 1971, John F. Kennedy gravesite, Arlington Cemetery, 1964-1965 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Washington Scenes-Robert Kennedy funeral gravesite, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Washington Scenes-Robert Kennedy funeral gravesite, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Washington Scenes-Lincoln Memorial, 1966-1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, Lincoln Memorial Event, 09/1967 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1965-1967 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1967-1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11)
    Located in Box 20 of shared box.
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1969 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Washington Scenes-Meet the Press, 1970-1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Washington Scenes-National Cathedral, 1971-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Washington Scenes-National Christmas tree lighting, 1970-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Washington Scenes-National Christmas tree lightening with Jimmy Carter, 1978 ca. (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Washington Scenes-News Shows in Washington, 1980, 1982 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Washington Scenes-News Shows in Washington, 1972-1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Washington Scenes-Nixon Inaugural, 1969, Washington Scenes-Potomac Flood, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Washington Scenes-Tidal Basin/cherry trees, 1966-1967, Washington Monument, 1965-1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Washington Scenes-White House, 1965 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Washington Scenes-White House, 1966-1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Washington Scenes-White House, 06/1973-07/1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Washington Scenes-White House, 06/1973-07/1973 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Washington Scenes-White House reception on South Lawn, 06/1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Washington Scenes-Miscellaneous, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 15)
    Contains photographs of the following buildings: 16th and L St. NW,1971; American Nazi Party protest,1965; Blair House,1974; C & O Canal;Chinatown parade,1973; Concert on Potomac site of Kennedy Center,1969; Dulles airport,1969; Hubert Humphrey lying in state at Capitol Rotunda (?),1978; Iwa Jima Memorial, 1971,1974; Library of Congress, 1971,1974; Mount Vernon,1965; National Archives,1971; Old Executive Office Building,1976; Pennsylvania Ave.,1974; Resurrection city,1968; RFK stadium,1965; St. John's Church,1974; Veteran's Day protest,1969; Watergate Hotel.
  - Washington Scenes-Miscellaneous, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1958-1962 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1962-1964 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1964-1966 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1966-1967 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11)
    Located in Box 21 of shared box.
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1967-1968 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1967-1970 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1971-1972 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1972-1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1975 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, 1975-1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ron Howard - Trip to USSR, 1983 (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Ron Howard - Personal slides, undated (Box SHARED Box 11, Box 21, Folder 18)